Win Win Naing

A web developer

No. (225) Khayae Street South Dagon Township Yangon +95 420 068 738 winwinnaing223@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Werkz Technologies Co.,Ltd, Yangon branch of Amdon Consulting Pte Ltd — Web Developer

December 2019 - Present

Amdon Consulting Group is the region's leading provider of interactive content and inquiry-based pedagogical resources, especially in the fields of Science and Technology.

The primary tasks were to develop education websites. The Technologies for the products are Angular 1/2, html, css, javascript, nwjs.

JOBDOH Co.,Ltd, Yangon branch of Hong Kong — Full Stack Engineer

July 2019 - November 2019

The primary task is to develop the mobile application. The Technologies for the products are native vue, vuejs, graphql, firebase.

- Developed mobile application
- Wrote Unit tests
- Deployed application to app store
- Developed web page if necessary

Werkz Technologies Co.,Ltd, Yangon branch of Amdon Consulting Pte Ltd — Javascript Developer

April 2017 - June 2019

Amdon Consulting Group is the region's leading provider of interactive content and inquiry-based pedagogical resources, especially in the fields of Science and Technology.

The primary tasks were to develop many education games by communicating with designer team from Manila. The Technologies for the products are hype, Adobe Muse, jQuery, javaScript and sqLite.

Leaded the team and trained juniors.

Learned nim programming language and developed a small project within one week.

Wedtexts, Remote—Full Stack Developer

Sep 2016 - Feb 2017

Get training from CTO who has over 20 years of experience in software industry . Joined as a full stack developer on MEAN stack product.

Developed backend APIs.

Developed the product to version 2.0 with team.

Developed wedding scheduling website.

Enterprise Solution Co.,Ltd, Yangon—Junior Software Developer

July 2015 - Oct 2016

Modified Payroll software using VB and MySql Database.

Went to customer sites and trained to use the software and serviced their requirements about software.

EDUCATION

SEAMEO CHAT COMMUNICATION IN ENGLISH COURSE

2017-2019

Diploma in English

PC-One Software Developer Boot Camp

December 2015 - April 2016

The boot camp was one of a kind in which it focused more on training the mindset of a good qualified developer than the technical skills. Learnt the right attitude, and how to tackle the challenges of solving the software development problems.

University of Computer Studies, Yangon

2012-2015

Got the Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science $\mathbf{B.C.Sc}$

CONFIDENT SKILLS

AngularJS

Javascript

JQuery

Vue

Нуре

MySql

Frontend Web Development

PRODUCTION / WORKING KNOWLEDGE

React

VB

Nim

NodeJS (ExpressJS)

MySQL

MongoDB

graphql

Backend Web Development

SUMMARY

I believe myself I can do something that I want even I didn't have any experience about it. I loved Mathematic in school subjects since I was a student. I like finding the solutions, solving the problems and thinking about logic. So, software developing is an associated job for me. I also like new challenges and believe I will be able to win always.